Register of the John G. Veneman papers, 1959-1981
Hoover Institution Archives
- CORRESPONDENCE, 1969-1979 (Boxes 6-12)
  - Thomas, G. Pendleton (Box-folder 11: 50)
  - Thompson, George K. (Box-folder 11: 51)
  - Thompson, Zan (Box-folder 11: 52)
  - Timmons, William E. (Box-folder 11: 53)
  - Torrens, John R. (Box-folder 11: 54)
  - Towell, Nancy (Box-folder 11: 55)
  - Towell, Thomas (Box-folder 11: 56)
  - Train, Russell E, Mr. and Mrs. (Box-folder 11: 57)
  - Tuxhorn, Scott (Box-folder 11: 58)
  - Twiname, John D. (Box-folder 11: 59)
  - Underwood, Vernon (Box-folder 11: 60)
  - University of Alabama (Box-folder 11: 61)
  - Unruh, Jesse M. (Box-folder 11: 62)
  - Urion, Rick (Box-folder 11: 63)
  - Vestner, Eliot N., Jr. (Box-folder 11: 64)
  - Vickerman, John (Box-folder 11: 65)
  - Waldman, Raymond J. (Box-folder 11: 66)
  - Walker, Charls E. (Box-folder 11: 67)
  - Walker, Stephen (Box-folder 11: 68)
  - Walt, Harold R. (Box-folder 11: 69)
  - Walter, Judith (Box-folder 11: 70)
  - Walters, Robert G. (Box-folder 11: 71)
  - Washington Star (Box-folder 11: 72)
  - Watanabe, Robert (Box-folder 11: 73)
  - Weaver, Charles H. (Box-folder 11: 74)
  - Weinberger, Caspar W. (Box-folder 11: 75)
  - Weinstein, Sheridan L. (Box-folder 11: 76)
  - Welk, Robert (Box-folder 11: 77)
  - Welty, Alan (Box-folder 11: 78)
  - West, Robert V., Jr. (Box-folder 11: 79)
  - Wetterling, Jerry D. (Box-folder 11: 80)
  - Whiteman, Cynthia (Box-folder 12: 1)
  - Wice, Jeffrey (Box-folder 12: 2)
  - Wilck, C. Thomas (Box-folder 12: 3)
  - Will, Robert P. (Box-folder 12: 4)
  - Williams, George (Box-folder 12: 5)
  - Wilson, Bob (Box-folder 12: 6)
  - Wilson, Pete, Mr. and Mrs. (Box-folder 12: 7)
  - Wirth, Timothy E. (Box-folder 12: 8)
  - Wisely, Harold M. (Box-folder 12: 9)
  - Woods, George D. (Box-folder 12: 10)
  - Woolley, Sara (Box-folder 12: 11)
  - Wurm, Ross (Box-folder 12: 12)
  - Young, Andrew (Box-folder 12: 13)
  - Younger, Evelle J. (Box-folder 12: 14)
  - Zapolski, Joseph (Box-folder 12: 15)
  - Zenovich, George N. (Box-folder 12: 16)
- SPEECHES AND WRITINGS, 1965-1977 (Boxes 12-15)
  Articles, comments, notes, outlines, remarks, statements, speeches, and testimony, arranged chronologically by title. Typescripts unless otherwise noted.
  - General, 1969-1976 (Box-folder 12: 17)
  - "A Legislative Perspective on Child Protective Services,", undated (Box-folder 12: 18)
  - "A New Approach to Poverty,", undated (Box-folder 12: 19)
    Includes two versions.
  - "Egalitarianism - The Road to Mediocrity,", undated (Box-folder 12: 20)
    Includes an outline.
  - "Nixon and Busing," reply to WCBS-TV editorial, undated (Box-folder 12: 21)
  - "The New Federalism: Fiscal Relief for the States,", undated (Box-folder 12: 22)
  - "The State of American Welfare,", undated (Box-folder 12: 23)
  - "The Future of Public Health Care Programs in California," speech, 38th Annual Statewide Meeting, California State Chamber of Commerce, Biltmore Hotel, Los Angeles, California, 1965 December 9 (Box-folder 12: 24)
  - "The Future of Public Health Care Programs in California," printed copy, 1966 Spring (Box-folder 12: 25)
  - "The Legislative Horizon -- 1967," remarks, County Welfare Directors Association Annual Meeting, Yosemite Lodge, California, 1966 October 6 (Box-folder 12: 26)
  - "Woman's Responsibility in Government," remarks, Women's Society for Christian Service, Manteca, California, 1966 November 3 (Box-folder 12: 27)
  - "Government and the Nursing Home: Partnership...Or Else," remarks, California Association of Nursing Homes, Sanitariums, Rest Homes and Homes for the Aged, Inc. Convention, San Francisco, California, 1966 November 29 (Box-folder 12: 28)
  - Remarks, Auditors and Tax Collectors Association, Sheraton-Wilshire Hotel, Los Angeles, California, 1967 February 15 (Box-folder 12: 29)
  - "California's Fiscal Kaleidoscope," speech, 69th Annual Conference, League of California Cities Finance Officers Department, 1967 October 17 (Box-folder 12: 30)
  - "Property Tax Relief: The Legislative Approach to the Problem," speech, Valley Tax Conference sponsored by the California State Chamber of Commerce, Del Webb Townehouse, Fresno, California, 1967 October 26 (Box-folder 12: 31)
  - "A Fair Shake," speech, Taxpayers Association of Fresno County, Holiday Inn, Fresno, California, 1968 January 18 (Box-folder 12: 32)
  - "A Legislator Looks at Open Space Legislation," speech, Council of California Growers, Kona Kai Club, San Diego, California, 1968 February 14 (Box-folder 12: 33)
  - "Tax Picture in California," speech, California Municipal Utilities Association, Sheraton Palace, San Francisco, California, 1968 February 28 (Box-folder 12: 34)
  - Draft for speech, Stanislaus State College, 1968 February 29 (Box-folder 12: 35)
  - "Legal Rights of Children, Parents and the Law," speech, National Conference on Social Welfare, Civic Auditorium, San Francisco, California, 1968 May 30 (Box-folder 12: 36)
  - "The California Legislature," remarks, ITT Public Affairs Seminar, Hotel America, Washington, D.C., 1968 June 20 (Box-folder 12: 37)
  - Draft remarks, American Society for Public Administration, Washington, D.C., 1969 March 19 (Box-folder 12: 38)
  - Participant's comments, "Challenge from the Nixon Administration," Chamber of Commerce of the United States Closed-Circuit Teleconference, LOGOS Teleproduction Center, Arlington, Virginia, printed copy, 1969 March 26 (Box-folder 12: 39)
  - "The Government Program," speech, Association of Western Hospitals, Anaheim, California, 1969 April 28 (Box-folder 12: 40)
  - Address, 50th Anniversary Luncheon, Social Service Department, Providence Hospital, Washington, D.C., 1969 May 16 (Box-folder 12: 41)
  - Remarks, Annual Honor Awards Ceremony, Health, Education, and Welfare Region II, New York City, New York, 1969 May 23 (Box-folder 12: 42)
  - Outline notes for a speech, National Institute of Health Seminar, Science and Public Policy, Belmont, Maryland, 1969 May 25 (Box-folder 12: 43)
  - Address, Governor's Conference, Delivery of Health Services, Little Rock, Arkansas, 1969 May 27 (Box-folder 12: 44)
  - Address, 8th Annual National Convention, National Council of Senior Citizens, Washington, D.C., 1969 June 6 (Box-folder 12: 45)
  - Outline notes for a speech, National Advertising and Public Relations Conference, Blue Shield and Blue Cross, Washington, D.C., 1969 June 20 (Box-folder 12: 46)
  - Remarks, National Citizens Conference, Rehabilitation of the Disabled and Disadvantaged, Washington, D.C., 1969 June 24 (Box-folder 12: 47)
  - Outline notes for a speech, Legislative Council AFL-CIO, Washington, D.C., 1969 August 1 (Box-folder 12: 48)
  - Partial text of remarks, 71st Annual American Hospital Association Convention, International Amphitheatre, Chicago, Illinois, 1969 August 20 (Box-folder 12: 49)
  - Excerpts from remarks, Legislative Conference, Big Ten States, St. Louis, Missouri, 1969 August 28 (Box-folder 12: 50)
  - Partial text of remarks, Northeast Regional Conference, American Public Welfare Association, Baltimore, Maryland, 1969 September 8 (Box-folder 12: 51)
  - Excerpts from remarks, International Claim Association, Miami, Florida, 1969 September 22 (Box-folder 12: 52)
  - "Federal-State Relations: The National Trend," speech, Kentucky Media Conference, Louisville, Kentucky, 1969 September 24 (Box-folder 12: 53)
  - Speech, Anti-Defamation League, 1969 September 28 (Box-folder 12: 54)
  - Partial text of remarks, Annual Meeting, League of California Cities, San Francisco, California, 1969 October 1 (Box-folder 12: 55)
  - Excerpts from remarks, Dedication of Medical Science Buildings, Brown University, Providence, Rhode Island, 1969 October 4 (Box-folder 13: 1)
  - Partial text of remarks, Western Conference, Medical Care Plans, Sun Valley, Idaho, 1969 October 10 (Box-folder 13: 2)
  - Excerpts from remarks, Harvard University Faculty and Members of Harvard Schools Committee, Boston, Massachusetts, 1969 October 24 (Box-folder 13: 3)
  - Speech, County Welfare Directors Association of California, San Diego, California, 1969 October 29 (Box-folder 13: 4)
  - Partial text of remarks, 20th Annual Convention, American Nursing Home Association, Houston, Texas, 1969 November 6 (Box-folder 13: 5)
  - Excerpts from remarks, Western States Conference, Republican National Committee, Honolulu, Hawaii, 1969 November 7 (Box-folder 13: 6)
  - Address, Biennial Conference, Family Service Association of America, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1969 November 16 (Box-folder 13: 7)
  - Partial text of remarks, Dedication Ceremony, New Wing of NIMH Clinical Research Center, Lexington, Kentucky, 1969 November 25 (Box-folder 13: 8)
  - "Cooperative Role of Government and Industry in Dealing with Urban Problems," remarks, panel discussion, National Association of Manufacturers, New York City, New York, 1969 December 3 (Box-folder 13: 9)
    Delivered by Fred Malek for John Veneman.
  - Speech, Salute to Bill Bagley Dinner, St. Francis Hotel, San Francisco, California, 1969 December 11 (Box-folder 13: 10)
  - "The Social Work Profession on Trial," address, Golden Gate Chapter, National Association of Social Workers, San Francisco, California, 1969 December 12 (Box-folder 13: 11)
  - Partial text of remarks, National Council, Farmer Cooperatives Annual Meeting, Hollywood, Florida, 1970 January 14 (Box-folder 13: 12)
  - "The Improvement of National Health Care Problems," statement, Senate Committee on Finance, Silver Threads, printed copy, 1970 February 25 (Box-folder 13: 13)
  - Excerpts from remarks, Congressional-City Conference, National League of Cities, Washington, D.C., 1970 March 9 (Box-folder 13: 14)
  - Partial text of remarks, Governor's Conference on Community Health Services, Oklahoma City, Oklahoma, 1970 March 12 (Box-folder 13: 15)
  - Excerpts from remarks, Santa Clara County Chapter, National Conference of Christians and Jews, San Jose, California, 1970 March 31 (Box-folder 13: 16)
  - "The New Federalism: Fiscal Relief for the States," Tax Review, 1970 April (Box-folder 13: 17)
  - "The Republican Party and Drug Abuse," partial text of remarks, Republican Leadership Conference, Washington, D.C., 1970 April 17 (Box-folder 13: 18)
  - Excerpts from remarks, Goodwill Industries of Southern California, Los Angeles, California, 1970 April 23 (Box-folder 13: 19)
    Remarks prepared by Linda Hannaway for presentation by John Veneman. Includes re-write by Robert H. Finch, who delivered the speech.
  - Partial text of remarks, 50th Anniversary Convention, League of Women Voters, Washington, D.C., 1970 May 6 (Box-folder 13: 20)
  - Outline for remarks, Social Security Administration Forum, Baltimore, Maryland, 1970 May 8 (Box-folder 13: 21)
  - Partial text of remarks, Southwest Regional Conference, Child Welfare League of America, Fort Worth, Texas, 1970 May 10 (Box-folder 13: 22)
  - Excerpts from remarks, Gallaudet College Commencement, Washington, D.C., 1970 May 18 (Box-folder 13: 23)
  - Statement, Department of Health, Education, and Welfare Auditorium, North Building, Washington, D.C., transcript of proceedings, 1970 May 18 (Box-folder 13: 24)
  - Commencement address, College of Osteopathy and Surgery, Kansas City, Missouri, 1970 May 21 (Box-folder 13: 25)
    Address was delivered by James H. Cavanaugh, Deputy Assistant Secretary for Health, and Scientific Affairs.
  - Partial text of remarks, Americam Management Association, New York City, New York, 1970 June 11 (Box-folder 13: 26)
  - Excerpts from remarks, Commencement Exercises, University of California, Davis, College of Letters and Science, Davis, California, 1970 June 17 (Box-folder 13: 27)
  - Partial text of remarks, Testimonial Dinner in honor of State Senator Robert Lagomarsino, Oxnard, California, 1970 August 14 (Box-folder 13: 28)
  - Excerpts from remarks, Town Hall of California, Biltmore Hotel, Los Angeles, California, 1970 August 18 (Box-folder 13: 29)
  - Partial text of remarks, Biennial Convention, National Federation of Federal Employees, Sacramento, California, 1970 September 16 (Box-folder 13: 30)
  - Excerpts from remarks, College of Medicine, University of Iowa, Iowa, 1970 September 19 (Box-folder 13: 31)
  - Speech, Business Insurance Management Idea Workshop, Atlanta, Georgia, 1970 October 11 (Box-folder 13: 32)
  - Partial text of remarks, College of Data Processing, Los Angeles, California, 1970 October 26 (Box-folder 13: 33)
  - Outline for remarks, National Health Insurance Conference, 1970 November 12 (Box-folder 13: 34)
  - Remarks, Equal Opportunity Day Dinner, Essex County Urban League, Newark, New Jersey, 1970 November 17 (Box-folder 13: 35)
  - Speech, dedication of the Metropolitan Hospital for Extended Care, Washington, D.C., 1970 November 19 (Box-folder 13: 36)
    Delivered by Dr. James H. Cavanaugh.
  - Outline for remarks, Westinghouse Senior Executives, 1970 November 30 (Box-folder 13: 37)
  - Excerpts from remarks, Commercial Club of Boston Merchants Club, Boston, Massachusetts, 1970 December 8 (Box-folder 13: 38)
  - Partial text of remarks, Regional Commissioner's Environmental Manpower Administrative Teach-In, Asilomar, Pacific Grove, California, 1970 December 16 (Box-folder 13: 39)
    Delivered by Dr. Geo. Lowe?, Office of Education.
  - Excerpts from remarks, Channel City Club, Santa Barbara, California, 1970 December 17 (Box-folder 13: 40)
  - Remarks, Social Security Awards, 1971 January 6 (Box-folder 13: 41)
  - Partial text of remarks, Maricopa Medical Society, Phoenix, Arizona, 1971 January 9 (Box-folder 13: 42)
  - Excerpts from remarks, 71st Annual Dinner, Cathedral Club, New York City, New York, 1971 January 28 (Box-folder 13: 43)
  - Partial text of remarks, National Association of Manufacturers, Boca Raton, Florida, 1971 February 16 (Box-folder 13: 44)
  - Excerpts from remarks, American Association of University Women, Shoreham Hotel, Washington, D.C., 1971 February 17 (Box-folder 13: 45)
  - Outline for remarks, National Chamber of Commerce, 1971 March 11 (Box-folder 13: 46)
  - Partial text of remarks, Commonwealth Club of California, San Francisco, California, 1971 March 19 (Box-folder 13: 47)
  - Excerpts from remarks, Health Insurance Association of America, 1971 March 29 (Box-folder 13: 48)
  - Partial text of remarks, National Association of Counties, Washington, D.C., 1971 April 5 (Box-folder 13: 49)
  - Excerpts from remarks, Distinguished Service Awards Ceremony, National Institute of Health Auditorium, 1971 April 15 (Box-folder 13: 50)
  - Partial text of remarks, Medical Care Section, American Public Health Association and the University of Southern California School of Medicine, 1971 April 30 (Box-folder 13: 51)
  - Draft speech, Luncheon Meeting, Howard University, 1971 May 14 (Box-folder 13: 52)
  - Excerpts from remarks, American Pharmaceutical Manufacturers Association, White Sulphur Springs, West Virginia, 1971 May 24 (Box-folder 14: 1)
  - Partial text of remarks, Fifth Annual Medical Staff-Trustee-Administration Forum, Boyne Mountain, Michigan, 1971 May 26 (Box-folder 14: 2)
  - Outline for remarks, Group Health Association, 1971 June 3 (Box-folder 14: 3)
  - Excerpts from remarks, 1971 Group Health Institute, Group Health Association of America, Washington, D.C., 1971 June 3 (Box-folder 14: 4)
  - Talk, National Association of Manufacturers' Televised Program on the Occupational Safety and Health Act of 1970, 1971 June 15 (Box-folder 14: 5)
  - Partial text of remarks, Northeast Regional Media Briefing, Rochester, New York, 1971 June 18 (Box-folder 14: 6)
  - Remarks, Groundbreaking Ceremony, Bethune Memorial, Washington, D.C., 1971 June 19 (Box-folder 14: 7)
  - Excerpts from remarks, 23rd Annual Convention, Big Brothers of America, San Francisco, California, 1971 June 25 (Box-folder 14: 8)
  - Partial text of remarks, Eastern States Leaders Seminar, National Conference of State Legislative Leaders, Manchester, New Hampshire, 1971 July 11 (Box-folder 14: 9)
  - "Public Responsibility for Planning Health," excerpts from remarks, National Association of State Budget Officers, Clearwater, Florida, 1971 August 25 (Box-folder 14: 10)
  - Partial text of remarks, Comstock Club, Sacramento, California, 1971 September 13 (Box-folder 14: 11)
  - Excerpts from remarks, Fresno Chamber of Commerce, Fresno, California, 1971 September 14 (Box-folder 14: 12)
  - Remarks, Santa Cruz County Fair, Watsonville, California, 1971 September 15 (Box-folder 14: 13)
  - Excerpts from remarks, Pacific Forum on Mental Retardation, Honolulu, Hawaii, 1971 September 29 (Box-folder 14: 14)
  - Comments, Voice of America interview on United States Social Security System, Washington, D.C., 1971 September 30 (Box-folder 14: 15)
  - Partial text of remarks, Panel on National Health Insurance, American Public Health Association, Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1971 October 13 (Box-folder 14: 16)
  - Excerpts from remarks, 44th National Future Farmers of America Convention, Kansas City, Missouri, 1971 October 14 (Box-folder 14: 17)
  - Outline for comments, Health Seminar for Institutional Investors, Washington, D.C., 1971 October 15 (Box-folder 14: 18)
  - Testimony, Senate Aging Committee, Subcommittee on Long Term Care, Washington, D.C., 1971 October 28 (Box-folder 14: 19)
  - Partial text of remarks, National Pharmaceutical Council, Inc., Washington, D.C., 1971 November 4 (Box-folder 14: 20)
  - Speech, American Nursing Home Association, Anaheim, California, 1971 November 5 (Box-folder 14: 21)
  - Edited text of remarks, American Association of Homes for the Aging, Seattle, Washington, 1971 November 8 (Box-folder 14: 22)
  - Speech, National Association of Manufacturers Employee Benefits Committee, Washington, D.C., 1971 November 11 (Box-folder 14: 23)
  - Presentation, H.R. 1 Planning Task Force, Fort McNair, 1971 November 12 (Box-folder 14: 24)
  - Excerpts from remarks, National Municipal League, Atlanta, Georgia, 1971 November 16 (Box-folder 14: 25)
  - Remarks, United Cerebral Palsy of Greater Chicago, Chicago, Illinois, 1971 November 17 (Box-folder 14: 26)
  - Partial text of remarks, SS American Courier, Long Beach, California, 1971 November 30 (Box-folder 14: 27)
  - Speech, Council of State Governments, Washington, D.C., 1971 December 3 (Box-folder 14: 28)
  - Statement, Subcommittee on Public Health and Environment, House Committee on Interstate and Foreign Commerce, Washington, D.C., 1971 December 10 (Box-folder 14: 29)
  - Outline for speech, Los Angeles Area Chamber of Commerce, Los Angeles, California, 1971 December 14 (Box-folder 14: 30)
  - Excerpts from remarks, Los Angeles Board of Supervisors, Los Angeles, California, 1971 December 14 (Box-folder 14: 31)
  - Remarks, Lutheran Hospital Society of Southern California, Los Angeles, California, 1971 December 15 (Box-folder 14: 32)
  - "Gubernatorial Relations with the Administration," speech, Intergovernmental Relations Seminar, National Governors' Conference, Dauphene Room, Sonesta Hotel, Washington, D.C., 1972 January 13 (Box-folder 14: 33)
  - Excerpts from remarks, California State Polytechnic College, San Luis Obispo, California, second draft, 1972 January 19 (Box-folder 14: 34)
  - Partial text of remarks, San Luis Obispo Chamber of Commerce, San Luis Obispo, California, 1972 January 19 (Box-folder 14: 35)
  - Speech, Santa Clara Valley Skills Center, San Jose, California, 1972 January 20 (Box-folder 14: 36)
  - Introductory remarks, Republican Task Force on Health, Washington, D.C., 1972 January 26 (Box-folder 14: 37)
  - Statement on nursing home programs, 1972 February 4 (Box-folder 14: 38)
  - Excerpts from remarks, Arkansas General Assembly, Little Rock, Arkansas, 1972 February 10 (Box-folder 14: 39)
  - Remarks, California Hospital Association, Volunteer Services Division, San Francisco, California, 1972 February 11 (Box-folder 14: 40)
  - Partial text of remarks, Jaycee's Flemming Awards Luncheon, Washington, D.C., 1972 February 17 (Box-folder 14: 41)
  - Address, California Taxpayers' Association, 1972 February 28 (Box-folder 14: 42)
  - "Education and the Urban Crisis," excerpts from remarks, University of the Pacific, Stockton, California, 1972 February 29 (Box-folder 14: 43)
  - "Workfare under H.R. 1," remarks, Republican Group, 1972 March 2 (Box-folder 14: 44)
  - Partial text of remarks, Minnesota Welfare Association, Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1972 March 15 (Box-folder 14: 45)
  - Excerpts from remarks, 10th Anniversary, Manpower Development and Training Act, Washington, D.C., 1972 March 16 (Box-folder 14: 46)
  - Partial text of remarks, National Newspaper Convention, Washington, D.C., 1972 March 16 (Box-folder 14: 47)
  - Statement, Subcommittee on Fiscal Policy, Joint Economic Committee, Washington, D.C., 1972 March 20 (Box-folder 14: 48)
  - Excerpts from remarks, 1972 National Health Forum, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1972 March 21 (Box-folder 14: 49)
  - Statement, Welfare Children's March against H.R. 1, Washington, D.C., 1972 March 24 (Box-folder 14: 50)
  - Partial text of remarks, Alumni Postgraduate Convention, Loma Linda University School of Medicine, Los Angeles, California, 1972 March 29 (Box-folder 15: 1)
  - Welcoming remarks, Health Message Workshop, Dulles-Marriott Motel, Dulles Airport, Washington, D.C., 1972 April 4 (Box-folder 15: 2)
  - Excerpts from remarks, World Health Exhibit, Smithsonian Institution, Washington, D.C., 1972 April 7 (Box-folder 15: 3)
  - Partial text of remarks, Department of Health, Education and Welfare Honor Awards Ceremony, Washington, D.C., 1972 April 13 (Box-folder 15: 4)
  - "Pros and Cons of National Health Insurance," excerpts from remarks, Milwaukee Sentinel's 9th Annual Forum for Progress, Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 1972 May 1 (Box-folder 15: 5)
  - Partial text of remarks, National Retired Teachers Association, Miami, Florida, 1972 May 3 (Box-folder 15: 6)
  - Excerpts from remarks, Town Hall of California, Los Angeles, California, 1972 May 23 (Box-folder 15: 7)
  - Partial text of remarks, League of United Latin American Citizens, Santa Monica, California, 1972 May 27 (Box-folder 15: 8)
  - Excerpts from remarks, Commissioned Corps Joint Meeting, New York City, New York, 1972 June 1 (Box-folder 15: 9)
  - Partial text of remarks, AMA State President's Panel on Government and Medicine, San Francisco, California, 1972 June 17 (Box-folder 15: 10)
  - Excerpts from remarks, Los Angeles Rotary, Los Angeles, California, 1972 July 7 (Box-folder 15: 11)
  - Partial text of remarks, Dedication of Chippenham Hospital, Richmond, Virginia, 1972 July 16 (Box-folder 15: 12)
  - "The Political and Economic Realities of Welfare Reform," excerpts from remarks, Northeast Regional Conference, San Juan, Puerto Rico, 1972 September 6 (Box-folder 15: 13)
  - Statement, Subcommittee on Fiscal Policy, Joint Economic Committee, Washington, D.C., 1972 September 12 (Box-folder 15: 14)
  - Partial text of remarks, 4th Annual William D. Witter Inc. Health Industry Seminar, New York City, New York, 1972 October 5 (Box-folder 15: 15)
  - "The Best Game in Town," excerpts from remarks, United Crusade, Modesto, California, 1972 October 6 (Box-folder 15: 16)
  - Partial text of remarks, 28th Annual Convention, National-California League of Senior Citizens, Fresno, California, 1972 October 7 (Box-folder 15: 17)
  - Excerpts from remarks, Annual Meeting, American Academy of Pediatrics, New York City, New York, 1972 October 14 (Box-folder 15: 18)
  - "Drug Abuse Control - More Than Money," partial text of remarks, Annual Leadership Conference, American Health Association, New York City, New York, 1972 November 2 (Box-folder 15: 19)
  - "Nursing Homes and H.R. 1," partial text of remarks, Annual Convention, California Association of Nursing Homes, Sanitariums, Rest Homes and Homes for the Aged, Inc., Las Vegas, Nevada, 1972 November 14 (Box-folder 15: 20)